executionists.com 2019-03-16

# None

This Privacy Policy covers the privacy practices for Executionists.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. This policy was last updated on 6/28/18.

### Who We Are

Our website address is: https://www.executionists.com  
**Contact info:**  
info@executionists.com  
(424) 245-5472  
4134 Del Rey Ave.  
Marina del Rey, CA 90292

### **What personal data we collect and why we collect it**

We only collect information that you voluntarily give us via direct contact, via forms on this website and emails we receive.

We will only use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to learn more about our services or third party product offers. Except as expressly set forth herein, we will never loan, give away, sell, distribute or rent your personal information to any third party.

In order to acquire a free consultation on this website, a user must first complete the consultation form. In this form, a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the services or products on our site in which you have expressed interest.

We use various 3rd party modules on our website such as [Disqus](https://blog.disqus.com/update-on-privacy-and-gdpr-compliance) and MailChimp. Disqus users can log in to Disqus to adjust their settings on the Disqus website, including the Do Not Track option.

**Comments**  
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

**Media  
**If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

**Contact forms  
**We capture the data you submit in the contact forms on our website. It is stored in our database indefinitely unless you request to be removed. If you have requested to join our email list then you can always out of by clicking “unsubscribe” at the bottom of those emails when you receive them or email us to be removed from the email marketing list.

**Cookies  
**If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to save your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

**Embedded content from other websites**  
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely, until or unless we delete it. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.  
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### What rights you have over your data

You can request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Analytics

We use plugins to track our Google Analytics to help us improve our website experience. This data is anonymized.

### Who we share your data with

We do not share our data with other marketing agencies.

### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### How we protect your data

Our website is hosted on Pantheon.io’s servers, which are highly secure and use TLS encryption.

### Links

Where the Executionists website contains links to other sites, please be aware that Executionists is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave any of our sites and to read the Privacy Policies of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Executionists.

### Testimonials

Testimonials appearing on this site are actual feedback received via text, audio or video submission from our clients. They are individual experiences, reflecting real life experiences of those who have actually used our services. However, they are individual results and results vary. We do not claim that they are typical results that consumers will generally achieve. The testimonials are not necessarily representative of all of those who will use our services.

The testimonials displayed (text, audio and/or video) are given verbatim except for correction of grammatical or typing errors. Some have been shortened. In other words, not the whole message received by the testimonial writer is displayed, when it seemed lengthy or not the whole testimonial seemed relevant for the general public. The individuals providing these testimonials were not paid.

### Notification of Changes

We reserve the right to change or modify our privacy practices that are described herein simply by posting a revised Privacy Policy on this Website. Any such change shall be effective immediately upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy on this Website. We reserve the right to make the revised or changed Privacy Policy effective for information we already have about you, as well as any information we receive in the future. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy practices.

### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Executionists may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on the Executionists website.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of Executionists, Inc., or your dealings with the Executionists Website, please contact us at the following address: **[info@executionists.com](mailto:info@executionists.com)**
